[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Before the accident he did not ____ his guns locked or unloaded; now he does.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ventures like Amazon.com will only continue to ____ as long as they make money.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ in science or engineering usually pays more than one in manufacturing.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They have made a ____ error in the way they are thinking about the opportunities and problems their business face.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a widespread ____ that scaling up HIV voluntary counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This article will only ____ the issues rather than present a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The book is an educational and approachable reference in a difficult ____ of medicine where clinicians often feel uncertain.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ____ that the way we talk must not offend any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying ____ science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the operation may just ____ the problems.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The result of the school's drive to ____ student eating habits is that far fewer plates of French fries are now sold in the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She said that she will ____ to do better next trimester, but I'm not sure I believe her.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family member for the rest of their life ____ to this terrible form of cancer and they will deserve to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "From the beginning he has shown a hostile ____ to being in Germany and learning the German language.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Revenue from income tax is expected to be lower this year than in ____ years.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will facilitate growth and development in our ____ communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to manufacture ____ missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students will learn to appreciate what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an ____ are associated.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have subsequent problems than children in more ____ placements.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He's having a lot of problems learning English, ____ in grammar and spelling.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now dispute the ____ for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If your parents want too take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some people the ____ characteristics of a website are more important than its content.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was not willing to retreat from ____ legal commitments.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A major problem for most western societies is how to ____ immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The system uses a novel inference engine that does not ____ users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The construction of new facilities is an ____ for any university to make a clear statement about its environmental concern.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not appreciate the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a ____ racial identity.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be ____ the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company had to ____ their profit predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is ____ that the summer rate cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many countries have a ____ wage - this is the smallest amount of money that people may earn for a full-time job.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people ____ the ban on smoking in public places, but the majority are in favour of it.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Research has indicated that the majority of teachers failed to ____ computers in direct classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a ____ idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every effort to ____ young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an ____ security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In infants without a family history of food allergies, there is no need to restrict or ____ any specific foods.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will ____ in a series of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before buying a new house you need to ____ a tax advisor.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In order to claim a project, you must ____ a team of 3 to 6 people within a class and get verbal approval from your professor.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Facts surrounding the ____ of the child's condition are in serious dispute.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was a sound idea to ____ the problem before attempting attempt a solution.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This validation will identify him/her as a \"special student\" and will ____ him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would ____ at its current location on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to forego graduate or professional education because of lack of ____ to such programs.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This means that you will be able to ____ money from your bank account to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must ____ it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course is intended to ____ a lot of class discussion.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Preparing yourself for a ____ in oceanography is probably one of the most interesting and rewarding (yet difficult) paths to travel.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When traveling off-road, the car sensors must be able to ____ negative obstacles such as holes and ditches as well as positive ones such as trees or other cars.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was ____ yesterday for the third time this month. I presume he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a ____ rise in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unless we ____ the trend, the consequence will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of staff scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "show"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are so many careers that ____ Astronomy.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people say that drugs like cannabis should be made legal to allow the government to ____ its sale.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Downloading and reading this letter does not ____ acceptance to the First-Year course.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists are hoping that it may soon be possible to ____ the weather.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Research has indicated that the majority of teachers failed to ____ computers in direct classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The heroes of the stories in this book are people who speak only with ____ about their tragic histories.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government tried hard to ____ its decision, but most people believe it was a serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the ____ damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an adequate amount of ____ colostrum, the calf may not be able to resist disease.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school's ____ were told that they would not be getting an increase of pay in the new year.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would generate enough money so they refused to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ____ parent and enormous friction developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since we can't ____ it directly, we need to infer it from the things we can ____.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your condition is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and ____ the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Which do you ____ the more: health or wealth?", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "First, you will need to ____ background information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors occasionally make mistakes which can have ____ or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The President will ____ on TV this evening to talk about the riots in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the ____ and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should ____ to the topic sentence.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has only loose ____ of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will drain students of their ____ to think for themselves if you never set them challenging questions.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A serious problem of nuclear power is where and how to ____ of the radioactive waste.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the government's decision to invade Iraq.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He did not ____ the problem until too late.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She will ____ her chances of attending university if she doesn't start working harder.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief description of the storyline, or a brief ____ from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most language lessons ____ the chance for the students to practise speaking.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They did not ____ an attack. They responded to an attack from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once a language has less than about a hundred speakers, it is almost impossible to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a massive ____ of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Education has reduced the rate at which the disease has ____ throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and ____ discontent has arisen among the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Don't ____ me in your plan - I want nothing to do with it.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must differentiate ____ for students.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is certain to ____ opposition to its proposal.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Demonstrators tried to ____ the opening of the new airport runway.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to fail to prepare properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Contact between infected and uninfected people can ____ disease.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has come under pressure to ____ the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our results did not ____ us to determine whether SMR or MOEE had reached minimum values.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is principally because they ____ the church and family as sources of emotional support.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Repeat this ____ until only a small amount of pressure is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always fare well here, where patients may drive several hours to ____ medical care.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to invest a lot of ____ over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He has a strong bias ____ religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot ____ global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The results suggest that the best models will almost always ____ both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a flexible policy that can respond and ____ to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We used this information to construct a continuous measure of the ____ of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An ____ amount of research has been conducted into the mechanism by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before becoming a teacher she worked in the ____ of green technologies.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Despite the political, economic and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not ____ into the interior of East.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A primary goal of teaching is conveying ____ knowledge of the subject matter while inculcating curiosity, generating interest, and developing independence.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has recently published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The ____ has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have had no chance to examine changes of this sort systematically, but simply ____ them as examples of processes that we expect to be completed.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The problem is that parents start to ____ the expectation that we will provide unlimited services and that's just not feasible.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A simple and often effective ____ to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the volume of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an ____ for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people are ____ of the problem of global warming, but not many are willing to change the way they live.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some new students to the school find it unusual that teachers expect them to ____ with other students to complete homework assignments.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Health Minister has made the reasonable ____ that parents make sure their children eat enough fruit and vegetables.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free ____ of religion did not entitle an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an ____ tool for university life and work, and a valuable privilege.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ your instinct as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most ____ resource of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all ____ purposes.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an ____ in community and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are recommended to record every significant ____ about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school needs to address the serious problem of bullying ____ grade 7 students.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with medium grades who ____ help.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small ____ was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was an ____ in how new communication technologies could serve a community's educational goals.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The loose and often unclear ____ of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next ____ of the writing process is to edit it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The parents decided to ____ against the school's expulsion their son.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a ____ domestic situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Later in 1975, the APA announced that homosexuality was not a ____ disorder and in 1994 they acknowledged that it was neither a ____ illness nor a moral deficiency.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A series of accidents and a mounting public ____ resulted in the government licensing of pilots and aircraft.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An important clue to understanding volcanoes is knowing the ____ of the volcanic bands.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we want this plan to be a success, we need to ____ our resources very carefully.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He uses Blanche White to ____ the problems of color and class difference between blacks and whites.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this article I will ____ the possible use of automatic speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The parent appears to have a serious ____ of understanding of child development, resulting in unrealistic expectations for child that may be harmful.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first ____ of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She was in ____ with her parents at home and this was having a negative effect on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's own development to be a significant ____ in the educational process of the children.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above ____ course activities.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are ____ to risk sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a convenient way to ____ energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's own development to be a significant factor in the educational ____ of the children.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to ____ further ways to continue this great benefit to the company's staff as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the ____ation, we will make reasonable efforts to ____ others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many learners of English have problems with the spelling. Furthermore, many Asian students find the articles ____ difficult to use correctly.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have made ____ progress in English this trimester.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Carrying a large ____ of money is not a crime.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to seek assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to appeal ____ exclusion.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My father's ____ in Germany will terminate at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The outcome of the ____ remains very much in doubt.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and hence it should constitute the ____ of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the ____ of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The whole new industry of purchasing drugs \"on line\" is another area where care and ____ sense are essential.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to ____ a new strategy. This one isn't working.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many economists ____ the rise in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into ____ diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your final writing must correlate to your ____ notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is going to ____ a law that will prohibit smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing ____ laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not consistent with one another.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous ____ institution in the USA.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's not enough to ____ something; you have to work hard to achieve it.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can ____ a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this ____ will require the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a ____ problem, and its solutions will require new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers should not ____ the discussion or act as the last word on a student's artwork.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the ____ damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police ____ that they are doing all they can to find the missing child.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be brief and to ____ all that is important.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individuals should report the ____ to a faculty or staff member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In many cases print journals are disappearing as librarians strive to ____ money and shelf space.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to determine ____ disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, no one criterion will be the ____ reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Health Department is advertising on TV to ____ the message about the importance of healthy eating and exercise.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the actual and ____ effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What ____ of students at this come comes from Asia? - About 35% I think!", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to represent information about patterns of ties ____ social actors.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "About a quarter of the elementary and secondary students typically did not ____ with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In history class this year, we will ____ the French and Russian revolutions.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ the methods and texts advocated by these educators with the powerful ideas of the critical pedagogues shaping his opinions.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to adjust to ____ living.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most schools do a lot to ____ their students of the dangers of smoking.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the ____ still did not have time to cover all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will ____ due to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I need to ____ again that you may not use your calculator in the examination.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the ____ of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Germany had to ____ a harsh peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and occasionally requires travel away from the normal ____ station.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "European governments strongly condemn the kidnapping of a German ____ worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the words 'uninterested ' and 'disinterested'.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Yet there were conflicts there too, and the immigrants did not ____ easily and completely into Israeli culture.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ aims at helping students acquire a working familiarity with the Federal Rules of Evidence.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer ____ cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ____ puzzle involving three pegs, and an arbitrary number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The quality of your work has improved ____ in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to introduce ____ working times.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Before economists ____ drastic measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I gave him clear ____ how to do the experiment, but he obviously wasn't listening.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although the amendment claimed to reduce opportunities for voter fraud, it did not ____ the more common problems of fraudulent voter registration.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He said the debate now should ____ events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Conversely, rising wage rates often ____ workers to try to work fewer hours as they become rich enough to afford more leisure.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people believe that the government will not ____ with its plans to decriminalize cannabis.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Racism and prejudice ____ to be a major problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He continues to ____ all our efforts to help him.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When a student comes to a lesson having learned a ____ habit, time and money are lost and progress is postponed.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If there is a group that we have paid no ____ to, it's old women, says Hawkes.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The use of this seemingly simple system does not ____ an undeveloped technological ability on the part of 9th century Hindus.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to deprive people of the ____ to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always ____ the recommendations of the teachers about the course choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very confident that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at ____ to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The forecast was for travel ____ to increase by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Can you please use a ____ ruler to draw straight lines, not the side of your book.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to dramatically ____ the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We wish to ____ women who want to invent, create, and design the next generation of computers, and computing methodology.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we ____ that the dimension of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I speculate that she will not be given a ____ job at the school.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we are to ____ actions designed to reverse the pattern of current difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The administrative staff will ____ the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other ____ation.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; rather they ____ conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences arise which might ____ to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ____ the smooth progress of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to ____ contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a ____ basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are strict laws that ____ the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "China also experienced social upheaval, and was unable to ____ foreign domination of its trade.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are an individual with a ____ disability, you may be eligible to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not ____ us to abandon the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "From the ____ of the writing I can only infer that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new swimming facility for the 2008 Olympics in Peking will ____ many people from their current homes.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "University staff will ____ the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Downloading and reading this letter does not ____ acceptance to the First-Year course.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Once your webpages look the way you want, and are ready to ____ to the web, click the button located near the top of the screen.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most comprehensive ____ of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to ____ a current bank statement showing that you have enough funds to cover expenses.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The proposed changes to the new law will ____ it of all its power.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a direct result of how the black hole deforms space and time, a four-dimensional ____ that Einstein called spacetime.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What motives have ____ incited him to overcome all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Farmers ____ their crops. This means that they do not grow the same thing on the same field for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ phase of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are going on the field trip, do not forget to ____ if you need a special diet.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you want to make an ____ measurement of the weight of very small objects, you will need a special electronic balance.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Probably every introductory science text in the world includes a first chapter ____ on the scientific method.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is planning to set up an ____ to document climate change.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Beyond this, if you have a credible reason for absence or coming in late, such as a documented medical excuse, you should ____ that information to the instructor.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you change your ____ or place of study, please amend your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Tests are ____ when they measure what they claim to measure, and reliable when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Immigrants ____ more than 20% of the total population.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He came up with a ____ excuse for not doing his homework, but his teacher did not believe him.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right mixture of ____ that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time prior to the ____ date.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "San Francisco's ____ reform program is barely alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to ____ his reply to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ teaching methodology will not be successful in a class with many different nationalities and abilities.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Parents and children often ____ in their opinions on the importance of keeping bedrooms clean and tidy.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Caesar showed no ____ to accept the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "general"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In many cases print journals are disappearing as librarians strive to ____ money and shelf space.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students must ____ a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical passage into English.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences ____ which might contribute to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You should expect ____ grading of all assignments.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Recent years have seen significant ____ in scholarship on the history of telecommunications and related technologies.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is often necessary to ____ a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I am an American clergywoman with the unusual ____ of teaching these young people the Hebrew language, in Arabic.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Soviet workers have suffered a terrible ____ of a world-historical significance.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has introduced a ____ language course for immigrants who cannot speak English.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to ____ poor work that is due to laziness and poor work that is due to inability.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The intelligence ____ is finding it very difficult to determine which young men are likely to become terrorists and which are not.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If it doesn't print clearly after ____ cleanings, you will need to replace the print cartridge.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To ____ the highest positions in American politics it is necessary to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Later in 1975, the APA announced that homosexuality was not a ____ disorder and in 1994 they acknowledged that it was neither a ____ illness nor a moral deficiency.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The supervisor will ____ whether the paper is satisfactory, and thus she or he should make sure the student has enough preparation.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the ____ is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The way that people are raised as children will usually ____ the way that they act as adults.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug ____ underlie many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to ____ over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The owner of the organization has the ____ to make decisions.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is usually easy for teachers to ____ if an ESL student has copied text from a webpage.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer enter or ____ grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All political parties must ____ in their proposals to stamp out racism.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no ____ in getting angry with security staff at airports. They have no choice but to follow orders.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The hypothesis put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the ____ condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It quickly became apparent, however, that someone forgot to ____ the president of this decision.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need basic skills education and don't get it ____ in college.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Why do people still ____ in living near volcanoes?", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Do not ____ the serious error of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously ____ your overall grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's new proposals are too vague. They need to be ____ about what they expect people to do.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you don't need your old furniture, you could ____ it to the youth club.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Do you ____ a valid, current driver's licence?", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each student's ____ was so varied that I was unable to isolate common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a thorough ____ describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on ____ and condition.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to the ____ shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to assemble a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "last"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not ____ enough are the most likely to suffer from it.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs elementary competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are ____ with the popular belief that alcohol intoxication causes males to view women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not ____ to university business must be limited and must not interfere in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an ____ separate from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to exert ____ in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school made a mistake when buying new computers. They are not ____ with the printers we have.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Once you've chosen the ____ or ____s you wish to take, you should contact COM so that we can reserve a place for you.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new government proposals also stipulate that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training ____ once a year.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing damage is a ____ problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power cycle failure, but this is not a ____ for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Austen does not convince us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and ____ in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to ____ the impact of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of most big cities around the main train station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Before buying a new house you need to ____ a tax advisor.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you change your address or place of study, please ____ your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company does a ____ amount of business in the USA; the majority of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to improve in English, I recommend that you read ____ of books for pleasure.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter ____ to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Being the best tennis player in grade 7 is not enough to ____ you for the ISST sports competition.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the Olympic Games is five overlapping rings.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This document contains a ____ of what scientists think happened at Loihi in the summer of 1996, based upon geological, geophysical, geochemical and biological evidence.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A common cause of ____ between the teacher and a student, when the student comes late to class for no good reason.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some farmers, ____ those producing corn, hope that biofuels have a bright future, both as a new source of cheap energy and as a new source of revenue.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must contact the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to ____ the book.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ocean floor is the last great ____ waiting to be exploited for its oil and other minerals.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ optional parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very confident that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at ____ to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Soviet workers have suffered a terrible ____ of a world-historical significance.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not yield more ____ results.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please write a ____ of the most important causes of the French Revolution.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war ____ Iraq.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These were very industrialized nations but their economies did not ____ the high levels of consumer spending we see in the First World.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the words 'uninterested ' and 'disinterested'.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global ____ will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always criticize them in private; this shows your ____ for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The online instructor must incorporate the best practices of traditional teaching without the ____ of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computer hard disk cleaning is not an ____ that many people perform very frequently.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists hope that in the future wind power will be able to ____ 50% of the electricity we need.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right mixture of ____ that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the ____ that she projected and the need to preserve her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to explain your ____ as clearly as possible and provide appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If your students are not at the ____ you have planned for them in the middle of the quarter, you will need to investigate why this is so.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lord Wavell had to ____ as he could not bring about a settlement and he was succeeded by Lord Mountbatten.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She stopped smoking and started exercising. As a ____ her health improved considerably.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "against"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family member for the rest of their life due to this terrible form of cancer and they will ____ to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can educators ____ instruction to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, indeed devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only ____ materials, not ones especially made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ is not only a local problem, but must be dealt with on a national level.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ the data further, you will see that there are many observations that are larger than 600.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her writing was ____ in every respect; it was difficult to isolate her biggest problem.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Quaranta envisions a future when computer simulations like this will be used to ____ a tumor's clinical progression.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She began to notice that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The sorting of students into homogeneous ____ and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with ____ grades who deserve help.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a ____ that is sometimes positive and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a controversial ____ that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to ____ or address the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The doctor began to realize that her patient was not telling the whole ____ about what was wrong.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not depart from the ____ requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What motives have ____ incited him to overcome all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been ____ in recent months, but prices are expected to fluctuate in the near future.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was only one ____ in a long struggle that did not come to a legal end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices gradually decreased until ____ zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What ____ of students at this come comes from Asia? - About 35% I think!", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was not the ____ of going to school; it was expected that you'd go to work and contribute to the family.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Abortion is not a fundamental right; it can be limited if the ____ wishes.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If two students are always talking in class, then the teacher will often ____ them and make them sit in opposite parts of the room.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much credit by conducting a ____ after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you possess a valid, ____ driver's licence?", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; ____ it has had little opportunity to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Copying from the internet has grown on a large ____ in recent years.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer rate cuts will ____ the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government needs to decide on a ____ response to the continuing violent demonstrations.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She needed to earn enough money to be able to ____ London's sky-high prices.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is planning to ____ all new mothers with a book advising them how to take care of their baby.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The cakes ____ of flour, sugar, eggs and milk.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company's ____ is that they will increase exports by 20% next year.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I conduct myself in a different ____ to different people.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The robot will ____ medications, and alert help if the patient falls.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The librarian will be able to ____ some good books for you to read in the summer vacation.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please write a brief ____ of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There will not be representative democracy in Iraq. Instead, there will be a long US-led ____ occupation that will incite resistance.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most ____ decision of his career in order to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was also faced with difficult questions about the university's handling of the emergency and whether it did enough to ____ students.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Customers found no ____ in comparison -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they ____ to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the ____ and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a loud argument in the cafeteria today. I had to ____ before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't appreciate a ____ from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A Parisian mob broke into the palace killing many of the guards, while searching for the ____ family.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ the missing information before submitting the form, otherwise it will be returned to you to complete.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The entire structure of Iraqi military and civil ____ collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ their plans after thousands of people demonstrated on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I often find it difficult to ____ my advice so that the ESL beginners in the class can understand me.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We ____ the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Each year the school has to import many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to import more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to ____ enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The American public seems prepared to ____ some privacy for security.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, ____ got into the habit of meeting together to discuss ideas.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Another ____ meaning of due is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is due tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I like teachers who can ____ clearly what we have to do.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "With her good grades she is now getting the ____ of all her hard work.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is never too late to ____ healthy habits! American Institute for Cancer Research.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to ____ the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The requirements threaten to decrease family and ____ student control over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not ____ ourselves and therefore our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individuals should report the incident to a faculty or staff ____ at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They ____ the food directly to needy families and individuals.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even though the right hemisphere could not ____ to observers what stimuli it had been presented with, it did show some verbal comprehension.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Scientists are working on a robot that can ____ to the deepest parts of the Pacific Ocean.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university's plan to ____ more students from poor backgrounds is an exercise that is not certain to succeed.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to protect yourself and your ____ are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "ESL students ____ better in classrooms where the teacher is aware of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Instead of getting involved in the affairs of other countries, the government should concentrate on its ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Very ____ water does not conduct electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Board will consider a leave for a President for a duration of ____ one month for each two years of service.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Major life events often ____ changes in financial planning strategies.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to protect yourself and your ____ are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Columbus did not ____ slavery to the New World; the practice existed there before his arrival.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ people without jobs to business that are looking for workers.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to ____ what is happening in Afghanistan, it is necessary to go there yourself.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In August, UMBC will ____ a new home page on our Web site.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a sample of its books to ____ to teachers.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and ____ discontent has arisen among the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your vocabulary test scores are good but you take twice as long to learn the words as the other students. You need to use a more ____ method.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He flew in with 500 rolls of film and 1400 pounds of provisions but forgot to ____ for the pilot to pick him up again.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has been an important exponent, nationally and internationally, of the view that artists have a critical ____ to play in democratic societies.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is set to ____ a heavy defeat in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or extend the building's ____ infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We are focused on creating the technology and applications that will ____ daily media consumers to become daily media producers.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ that we find better and cheaper ways to create energy than by burning coal or oil.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government ____ wrote to confirm that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A few years ago a robot was lowered to the seabed to ____ some objects from the wreck of the Titanic.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He said that he did not want to ____ the issue until the committee meeting.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Use positive words and phrases; don't ____ the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She will ____ her chances of attending university if she doesn't start working harder.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "However, as a dermatologist I felt the articles did not ____ strongly enough the possible drawbacks of the treatment.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ farmers who grow crops that can be used to run cars.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of our survey is that most students are against school uniform.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The President accepts full ____ for the decision to attempt the rescue.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board may ____ that those actions created a hostile or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The remaining 40 percent said that they were not familiar with the ____ 'sustainable agriculture'.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most beginning ESL students need a lot of ____ from their teachers and parents before they can start to work more independently.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to ____ in a way beyond words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The cost of gas (petrol) will continue to ____ as the price of oil goes up or down.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will ____ the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is among the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It would not be ____ to deviate from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Education Department's increased demand for paperwork will ____ the patience and good will of teachers.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Why do some children seem ____ to cooperate while others do not?", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ventures like Amazon.com will only continue to ____ as long as they make money.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ the problem until too late.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each section of the book, is represented by a family, which was chosen as an ____ family representing that country.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ____ that the way we talk must not offend any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite looking for Osama Bin Laden for many years, the USA still do not know his ____ location.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She chose to ____ the hypothesis that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The need for an alternative ____ to teacher certification has become evident.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no point in turning on the computer. The ____ isn't working.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Court did not find it ____ to hear the testimony of the two forensic experts and did not consider the possibility of ordering a further investigation.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to ____ by these two pieces, nor did I see any skill in the work.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our new system for handling lost ____ makes it possible for you to report the loss of belongings via Internet, on the telephone or at the counter.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Is anyone in class ____ with the terms 'subject' and 'predicate'?", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Recent research shows ____ against African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They did not ____ an attack. They responded to an attack from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not invest the ____ of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy demand to ____ costs.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I hesitate to put all of my ____ notes online because I do want students to attend the ____s.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The priests of this ____ did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the interpretation of dreams", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "First, you will need to gather ____ information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In general, when you paraphrase, you use about the same number of words to ____ the idea that the writer uses in the text.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices ____ decreased until virtually zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We can ____ that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such pressure.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some historians still ____ to label the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The robot will ____ medications, and alert help if the patient falls.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to get into university unless you have done well in school.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "No ____ can have much effect on the environment, but people working together can make a big difference.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many schools in poorer parts of the world do not have ____ books and computers to give their students a good education.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete ____ the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must ____ the US using the visa document issued by the institution you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has the ____ of protecting its citizens from terrorist attack, but many people do not agree with the way it is trying to do this.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone should ____ together to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One can fill a small book just describing the commonsense knowledge needed to ____ an ordinary problem like how to get to the airport.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should demonstrate a significant ____ of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is our ____ that the students were not given a fair hearing, and furthermore that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the adult victim acknowledges having experienced abuse, it is important to ____ the potential for future violence, as well as the danger involved.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This unnecessary ____ would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The role of doctors as a conscience of the community deserves more consideration in times of stress and under difficult ____ such as war.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lack of financial aid is a significant ____ on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to design and ____ a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to ____ new understanding.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The United Nations Commission of Human Rights did not ____ an investigation.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Numerous policy and ____ implications were derived from the study findings.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The water cycle is one of the natural processes that are ____ to most students.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Bright flashing lights ____ headaches in some people.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My regular mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a ____ for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another ____ to an already complex decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students receive feedback from the teacher on their ____ on the interpretative task before they start on the next one.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company plans to ____ training videos on its intranet website.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The communication medium is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have ____ to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the background information you will need to ____ some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is essential to consider her difficulties at school in the ____ of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Because southern Christian churches benefited financially from slave-based plantations they did nothing to ____ the practice of slavery.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to ____ commercial and financial practices in its member countries.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is English expression which claims: All roads lead to Rome. This means that there is more than one ____ to fame and success in life.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most scientists ____ that the life expectancy of people in developed countries will continue to rise.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a profound ____ on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not enough to ____ something; you have to work hard to achieve it.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It takes a lot of training to ____ the skills in professions such as car mechanics or cooking.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On the ____ occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The scientists that constitute the ____ all work in the field of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to ____ anonymous and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has the ____ that she can pass the examinations without doing any work.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is impossible to revive any Yuan play in its original style because the music is lost and its social ____ has changed.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The use of gender- ____ language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Military power is not an appropriate tool to ____ the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the essay is good, but the rest is of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company does a minor amount of business in the USA; the majority of its ____ is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Governments cannot govern without the broad ____ of the people.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The goal is to ____ world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the project will include all processes, people, organizational structures, systems and facilities currently in place.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This document will explain some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to ____ updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She will need an ____ performance to have any chance of winning the game. Her opponent is much better.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The reduced rainfall of recent years will ____ large parts of the country into desert.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the school cafeteria, you can buy drinks of different sizes: small, ____ and large.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's a ____ problem, and its solutions will require new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not enough to desire something; you have to work hard to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a ____ standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In 1993 a student wrote an article critical of Martin Luther King. The response was ____ and negative.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thanks to the ____ description of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The former assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more ____ idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government thanked Greenpeace for the information but said that it wasn't ____ to its decision.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are heading for a ____ in our health system. Not enough people want to be doctors.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the ____ cause of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not ____ between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ the reasons for your lack of success.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must contact the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to ____ the book.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a ____ loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes, the author will ask that the decision to ____ a paper be reconsidered.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We need to ____ access to new lands made possible by road expansion.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a ____ of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to ____ the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in order to give citizens the chance to review the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Can you please give me an ____ of what happened while I was out of the classroom?", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will ____ students of their ability to think for themselves if you never set them challenging questions.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This program will ____ entry to the field and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, ____ in the case of an independent investigation.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "That was a ____ question. Let me ask you any easier one.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher should ____ presentation styles and take into account diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Can someone please return this science equipment to the ____ cupboard?", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The settlers decided to ____ the settlement and sail back to Cuba.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ in the cafeteria after lunch.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ____ tells me that there is more to her learning problems than the parents are willing to say.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously ____ your overall grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Wonderwise is a ____ of educational packages introducing you to women who have made science their career.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ its report on adult education before the beginning of the summer vacation.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My ____ reaction was that something had happened to him on the way to school.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ to accept the idea that man is mere flotsam and jetsam in the river of life, unable to influence the unfolding events which surround him.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, no one criterion will be the ____ reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My biggest regret about the book is that Gruchy did not ____ his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ was abandoned in 1842 because the speeches had become too long and because students refused to shorten them.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people claim that the growth of the internet has been to the ____ of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they measure what they ____ to measure, and reliable when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some people God is an entity that influences every ____ of their life.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Terrorists ____ large areas of the country outside of the main towns.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My guess is that it had no ____ on prices except, possibly, the very first time, and that this ____ would probably have been very minor.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We are often right on the ____ of warm and cold or moist and dry air masses. So we get some very difficult weather conditions to try to forecast.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The following publications are ____ for purchase from the Florida Solar Energy Center.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should not ____ its tax policies on what newspaper editors tell it to do.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The doctor's claim was ____ hypocrisy. He more interested in making money than his patient's health.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the administration still did not have time to ____ all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief ____ of the storyline, or a brief episode from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "However, his proposal contains a fallacy that is important to ____ and understand.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student could not identify the ____ factors in a solution to the problem.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The supervisor perceived Pullard as an incompetent employee, but did not ____ that he might be a security problem.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was indeed a huge amount for a ____ that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This book provides the definitive ____ of the origins of coffee drinking.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the ____ eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a satisfactory ____ of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He also was able to ____ in identifying outstanding science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A rich parent has made a large ____ so that the school can buy new computers.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The most basic ____ to develop is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students will learn to ____ what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an outcome are associated.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Internet ____ has become extremely popular, but it's easy to waste time and find nothing useful.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Archaeologists can often come to an understanding of people who lived long ago just by examining the ____ of a pot or bone.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and ____ of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nevertheless, even within the ____ 1550-1850 there was a great deal of temperature variation both in time and space.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Before having a major surgical ____ patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the US government knew in advance about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At a certain ____ in your journey, you might discover that the topic you chose is just too vast.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school wanted to ____ students from families outside the usual sphere of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For most teachers the cash bonus was a nice acknowledgment of work well done, but not an ____ that influenced their behavior.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Melting glaciers will ____ Alpine ski resorts within 45 years, says report.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many of these strategies have already been adopted by the ____ airlines, which operate in an intensely competitive environment.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They did not provoke an ____. They responded to an ____ from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You must ____ the US using the visa document issued by the institution you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people ____ pictures to the emails they send.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The cold, hard truth is that your parents' generation was more open to experimentation, social change and an ____ 'looser' way of life.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no ____ about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is virtually dead.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our very privilege makes us ____ of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is only a ____ chance that she will pass her examinations. She has not been working well at in recent weeks.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "\"Be fair, ____ and friendly\" is the advice often given to new teachers.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ will include several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will recur in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the ____.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and ____ of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There will be no verbal or written personal attacks on any ____ or group of ____s based on age, ancestry, color, disability or handicap.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is considering whether to ban smoking in all ____ places.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She found, however, that there is no documented process for achieving a wise ____ to adversity.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in advance about the terrorist ____ on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "That's the third time she's been late in the last week. I think I need to ____ the matter with her parents.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the course is to have students discuss current events in Germany.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The \"Maximize\" position says that we should give priority to whatever ____ produces the greatest net health benefit.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He wants to get a job in the engineering ____ when he leaves school.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a sample of its books to ____ to teachers.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The assignments and quizzes form an integral part of the course grade and you may not ____ a good grade if you ignore them.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many economists ____ the rise in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Requiring students to leave the school building at lunchtime is not a very popular ____ from the new principal.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration ____ to modify its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She is unlikely to rise above the ____ of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}]]